<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>rofe33 on Raphael Tannous</title><link>https://raphaeltannous.com/</link><description>Recent content in rofe33 on Raphael Tannous</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://raphaeltannous.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One-Page Website Menu for Restaurants</title><link>https://raphaeltannous.com/services/one-page-website-menu-for-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raphaeltannous.com/services/one-page-website-menu-for-restaurants/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Welcome to One-Page Menu Website For Restaurants&lt;/strong>, where I specialize in creating a compact single page menu for restaurants.</description></item><item><title>Multi-Page Website Menu for Restaurants</title><link>https://raphaeltannous.com/services/multi-page-website-menu-for-restaurants/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raphaeltannous.com/services/multi-page-website-menu-for-restaurants/</guid><description>&lt;strong>Welcome to Multi-Page Website Menu For Restaurants&lt;/strong>, where I specialize in creating personalized websites/menu for restaurants. My service is tailored to meet your unique needs, offering a comprehensive solution to establish a strong online presence&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://raphaeltannous.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raphaeltannous.com/about/</guid><description>When I&amp;rsquo;m not in class, I enjoy exploring new free (as in freedom) and open-source software and learning about open-source tech.
I love writing code that&amp;rsquo;s both simple and safe.
Desktop Setup Operating System: Arch Linux Btw! Password Manager: KeepassXC Window Manager: Hyprland Web-Browser: Librewolf Terminal: foot Editor: Neovim Shell: Zsh</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://raphaeltannous.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://raphaeltannous.com/projects/</guid><description>Bibles - In a Bunch of Formats While learning and searching for something minimal, I came across Groff, short for GNU-troff, which is a typesetting system used for formatting and processing documents. I used the Mom macros to create some glorious bible PDFs, at the Github repo Bibles.
mpv-copyStuff mpv-copyStuff is a script for the mpv media player software. This script provides a way to copy video specific stuff to the system clipboard, like:</description></item></channel></rss>